+27 73 805 9845

Yazan Altaki

17 Nathan St, SE2, Vanderbijlpark ytaki2012@gmail.com

EDUCATION

IGCSE Certificate, Orbit Int. School

2015 - 2018

Diploma, Computer Systems, VUT

2019 - Current

LANGUAGES

Arabic, mother tongue English, fluent

SKILLS

- QT UI Designer
- Website Design and Coding
- 3D and PCB CAD Modeling
- Microcontroller Coding
- **SMath Studio**
- Microsoft Office

PROGRAMMING

- C/C++
- C# / Java
- Python
- HTML / CSS
- **SMath Equations**
- Assembly

OTHER QUALIFICATIONS

- CCNAv7 Certificate
- Various Udemy courses

ABOUT ME

A 23 year old aspiring programmer with an interest in art of all forms, not just illustrations or paintings. Currently studying full-time in the Vaal University of Technology (VUT) and about to start my sixth and final year. Whatever free private time I have, I mostly spend furthering my hobbies. My biggest objective is to design my own software framework for developing video games, and I envision myself completing this task from scratch with either a decade of part-time work, or half that of full-time work on this hobby, although it is not a high-priority goal.

You can stay in touch with my latest coding projects on my Github account.

WORK HISTORY

ROSEN Saudi Arabia

2018/06 - 2018/08

Workshop Assistant

I worked as a workshop assistant for two months (June to end of July). Rosen Saudi Arabia's main business is the non-destructive inspection of gas and oil pipelines. My main duty was to assist the engineering technicians in preparation and calibration of pigging tools.

During my internship, I have been exposed to and learnt the following skills and experiences:

- Using hand tools, workshop health and safety practices.
- Assembly of electrical/electronic components.
- Assembly of mechanical components.
- Working effectively and efficiently with a team.

Noble Aerospace

2023/07 - 2023/10

Junior Programmer

I worked as a programmer for Noble Aerospace's R&D department for three months (start of July to start of October) for my initial WBL semester. I was in charge of coding various functionalities and PC boards for their proprietary gyrocopters. I also had hands-on experience with designing and populating PC boards, as well as heavy use of Arduinos and STM32 modules.

During my stay, I have learned and honed the following skills:

- PCB design, populating, and soldering.
- Software and hardware uses of Arduino and STM32 modules.
- Application, research, and coding of components such as sensors.
- Planning and cooperating with coworkers and higher-ups.